<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>haakoo.github.io/</title>
   
   <link></link>
   <description>my ramblings about *</description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   <managingEditor> </managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>Happy with Ghost as my blogging platform</title>
	  <link>//happy-with-ghost-as-my-blogging-platform</link>
	  <author></author>
	  <pubDate>2015-07-30T20:09:00+00:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>//happy-with-ghost-as-my-blogging-platform</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Today I finally found the time to go back to my blog, it’s been a busy week and a half. One of the first things I usually do is to log on to <a href="http://ghost.slack.com">Ghost’s Slack</a> to see if there has been any activity. Today was no different and I was again happily surprised when browsing through the backlog in the channels.</p>

<p>The <a href="https://ghost.slack.com/messages/help/team/">Ghost team</a> isn’t large, but they are very active on their Slack and questions often get a reply within minutes. There are a lot of questions about Ghost, and almost every single one seems to have a simple solution. I’m getting a very good vibe about Ghost and the work that’s gone into it so far.</p>

<p>The team also answers a lot of non-Ghost questions, about anything from hosting (including <a href="https://www.digitalocean.com/">Digital Ocean</a> and other places) to configuring your webserver. It’s very reassuring to see such a competent team working on Ghost. I’m really looking forward to modifying <a href="https://github.com/haakoo/Findlay">my theme</a> and adding functionality in the coming months.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>Getting Ghost up and running on Mac OS X</title>
	  <link>//getting-ghost-up-and-running-on-mac-os-x</link>
	  <author></author>
	  <pubDate>2015-07-18T21:51:50+00:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>//getting-ghost-up-and-running-on-mac-os-x</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>I figured it would be nice to have Ghost up and running locally on my machine if I’m to mess around with themes. So today I installed <a href="https://nodejs.org/">Node.js</a>, cloned Ghost from <a href="https://github.com/TryGhost/Ghost">GitHub</a> and got it all working.</p>

<p>I followed the instructions from https://github.com/TryGhost/Ghost#developer-install-from-git with a few tweaks. You need to run the <code class="highlighter-rouge">npm install</code> commands using sudo (they will fail and then tell you to rerun as root). I also downloaded and installed Node.js v0.10.40 from <a href="http://blog.nodejs.org/release/">install package</a>. Node.js v0.10.40 has several security fixes and is probably a better choice than v0.10.36 I saw recommended somewhere.</p>

<p>Surprisingly easy to get it all running when I figured out that <code class="highlighter-rouge">npm install</code> needs root permissions and <code class="highlighter-rouge">grunt</code>does not after a tip from <a href="https://ghost.slack.com/archives/ghost/p1437257215000010">@acburdine in #ghost on Ghost Slack</a>.</p>

<p><em>Edit 2015-07-19:</em> It should be possible to run <code class="highlighter-rouge">npm install</code> without <code class="highlighter-rouge">sudo</code>, according to <a href="https://ghost.slack.com/archives/ghost/p1437262059000023">@fabian over at Ghost Slack</a>. I’ll see if I can reproduce my troubles from yesterday and figure out what was wrong.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>Choosing a comment system / platform</title>
	  <link>//choosing-a-comment-system-plattform</link>
	  <author></author>
	  <pubDate>2015-07-13T20:09:22+00:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>//choosing-a-comment-system-plattform</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>After playing with <a href="http://www.ghost.org">Ghost</a> for a couple of days I still haven’t figured out what to do with comments. Ideally I want something like Wordpress’ built in system, where you can post “anonymously” without registering and still get updates by email.</p>

<p>I have read a few blog posts recently that made me look at using Twitter for comments. That might work out for me, since I use Twitter so much, but not if I’m to use Ghost for other people’s blogs.</p>

<p>After I realised that <a href="https://disqus.com/websites/">Disqus</a> allows commenting without signing up I thought that might be a good fit. But they do not support notifications without signing up, and I do not want my readers to have to sign up to Disqus, so it’s not a perfect fit for me.</p>

<p>I looked at <a href="https://muut.com/">Muut</a> but it seems to be overkill for what I want (a simple comment system). The same goes for <a href="http://web.livefyre.com/">Livefyre</a>.</p>

<p>Since I want readers to post without signing up Facebook and Google+ comments are out of the question. It doesn’t help that I rarely use the services myself.</p>

<p>Then we have <a href="http://www.discourse.org/">Discourse</a>, but last time I looked it looked too focused on creating a “forum”, and not a comments system. I’ll have a new look at Discourse tomorrow.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
